 const data =[
    {
     question:"1. Which planet is closest to the Sun?",
     option1:"A. Venus",
     option2:"B. Mercury",
     option3:"C. Earth",
     option4:"D. Mars",
     ans:2
},
{
    question:"2. Which data structure organizes items in a First-In, First-Out (FIFO) manner?",
    option1:"A. Stack",
    option2:"B. Queue",
    option3:"C. Tree",
    option4:"D. Graph",
     ans:2
},
{
    question:"3. Which of the following is primarily used for structuring web pages?",
    option1:"A. Python",
    option2:"B. Java",
    option3:"C. HTML",
    option4:"D. C++",
     ans:3
},
{
    question:"4. Which chemical symbol stands for Gold?",
    option1:"A. Au",
    option2:"B. Gd",
    option3:"C. Ag",
    option4:"D. Pt",
     ans:1
},
{
    question:"5. Which of these processes is not typically involved in refining petroleum?",
    option1:"A. Fractional distillation",
    option2:"B. Cracking",
    option3:"C. Polymerization",
    option4:"D. Filtration",
     ans:4
},

{
    question:"6. What is the value of 12 + 28?",
    option1:"A.  45",
    option2:"B.  40",
    option3:"C.  67",
    option4:"D.  35",
    ans:2
},
{
    question:"7. How many states are there in the United States?",
    option1:"A.  65",
    option2:"B.  80",
    option3:"C.  50",
    option4:"D.  75",
    ans:3
},
{
    question:"8. In which year was the Declaration of Independence signed?",
    option1:"A.  1540",
    option2:"B.  2390",
    option3:"C.  2127",
    option4:"D.  1776",
    ans:4
},
{
    question:"9. What is the value of pi rounded to the nearest integer?",
    option1:"A.  3",
    option2:"B.  1",
    option3:"C.  5",
    option4:"D.  9",
    ans:1
},
{
    question:"10. If a car travels at 60 mph for 2 hours, how many miles does it travel?",
    option1:"A.  95",
    option2:"B.  100",
    option3:"C.  120",
    option4:"D.  140",
    ans:3
},
 
]

export default data;